// Create an array containing array ofobjects

const quiz = [
    {
        "Question": "When was the very first Legend of Zelda game released?",
        "Options": ["14, January 1997", "21, February 1986", "14, September 1985", "21, November 1991"], // Array of answers
        "Answer": 1
    },
    {
        "Question": "Which is the most recurring enemy in the Legend of Zelda series?",
        "Options": ["Keese", "Octorok", "Stalfos", "Like Like"],
        "Answer": 2
    },
    {
        "Question": "After which person was Zelda named after?",
        "Options": ["Zelda Fitzgerald", "Zelda Williams", "Zelda Harris", "Zelda Popkin"],
        "Answer": 0
    },
    {
        "Question": "Which game gives link the title: 'Hero of Light'",
        "Options": ["Four Sword Adventures", "Ocarina of Time", "Twilight Princess", "A link to the Past"],
        "Answer": 0
    },
    {
        "Question": "When was the Legend of Zelda animated series released?",
        "Options": ["21, August 1989", "25, December 1990", "7, March 1988", "8, September 1989"],
        "Answer": 3
    },
    {
        "Question": "Which of the four is NOT a Zelda CD-I game?",
        "Options": ["Link: The Faces of Evil", "Link: The Book of Truth", "Zelda's Adventure", "Zelda: The Wand of Gamelon"],
        "Answer": 1
    },
    {
        "Question": "Which game did the character 'Tingle' first appear in?",
        "Options": ["Wind Waker", "Oracle of Ages", "Majora's Mask", "Four Swords Adventures"],
        "Answer": 2
    },
    {
        "Question": "Which Link is used in Smash Bros. 4?",
        "Options": ["Skyward Sword Link", "Breath of the Wild Link", "Ocarina of Time Adult Link", "Twilight Princess Link"],
        "Answer": 3
    },
    {
        "Question": "How many shrines are there in Breath of The Wild? (No DLC)",
        "Options": ["120", "130", "110", "115"],
        "Answer": 0
    },
    {
        "Question": "Which of these Zelda games has the least amount of dungeons?",
        "Options": ["Breath of the Wild", "Majora's Mask", "Link's Awakening", "Wind Waker"],
        "Answer": 1
    },
    {
        "Question": "What is said by the old man in the original Legend of Zelda game?",
        "Options": ["'Take this! It's dangerous to go alone.'", "'It's dangerous out there! Take this.'", "'It's dangerous to go alone! Take this.'", "'It's dangerous!. Take this.'"],
        "Answer": 2
    },
]
